OCTA	B.S. Computer Science, University of Chicago Relevant Classes: Functional Programming, Computer Architecture  Javascript (2.5 years), HTML/CSS (5 years) Ruby/Rails (1 year), Python/Django (2 years) C (2 years), Java (1 year), Rust (<1 year), Elm (<1 year) MySQL (1.5 years), Access SQL (1 year), PostgreSQL (<1 year)  Research, Data, and Web Assistant, Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education (ACGME) Worked on a team to implement a major CMS update on the ACGME website by doing QA and user testing Worked as part of team updating the ACGME website content and created new pages using some HTML and CSS alongside a DNN (DotNetNuke) CMS system. Built the Residents and Fellows section of the ACGME website Assisted in writing and editing documentation on content submission, web request processes, and style guide Analyzed over 90 public comments and generated reports on common themes by writing a script to pull out common key words Built & maintained a political database of U.S. congress, generated reports detailing political figures and hospitals located within their areas of representation Created and facilitated a process for validating and organizing resources on Physician Well-Being to added to a resources database on the ACGME website Built a basic contacts database using SQL in access to be used for event management Temporary Assistant Web Manager, Cicerone Certification Program Built three international instances of website and migrated content from U.S. website to international websites Built online tools with Drupal 7.0 for user and product management for the online store on the website
	shawoj93@gmail.com   Github: ojshaw
EDUCATION	
2011 – 2015	
TECHNICAL SKILL	
	. Javascrint (2.5 years) HTMI /CSS (5 years)
EXPERIENCE	
Jan. 2017 – May 2018	
	<ul> <li>Worked on a team to implement a major CMS update on the ACGME website by</li> </ul>
	using some HTML and CSS alongside a DNN (DotNetNuke) CMS system.
	<ul> <li>Built the Residents and Fellows section of the ACGME website</li> </ul>
	writing a script to pull out common key words
	political figures and hospitals located within their areas of representation
	Well-Being to added to a resources database on the ACGME website
Aug. 2016 - Dec. 2016	· Built three international instances of website and migrated content from U.S. website
	· Built online tools with Drupal 7.0 for user and product management for the online
	Managed & updated user content & permissions through MySQL database
Sept. 2015 -	Freelance Web Development & Personal Projects
Present	<ul> <li>Worked on a one-page ticker website for National People's Action using Javascript</li> <li>Created a 3D Game of Life in Elm (a functional programming language)</li> </ul>
Oct. 2011 –	Student Assistant, Center for Health and Social Sciences (CHeSS)
Sept. 2014	<ul> <li>Updated the CHeSS website using Adobe Contribute/Dreamweaver and HTML &amp; CSS</li> </ul>
эсри. 2014	Managed computer inventory and updating of computer systems
June 2012 –	Residential Computing Assistant, Residential Computing at University of Chicago
June 2013	<ul> <li>Migrated, managed, and updated all residential computing websites and updated content for university housing website using HTML &amp; CSS and University's CMS</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Provided daily IT support during the summer and held weekly office hours during the school year in student housing</li> </ul>
	Upgraded computers and software by working as part of a team using UNIX shell
Aug. 2011	scripting to automate updates and computer imaging for setup of new workstations

## Aug. 2011

## Participant, Computer Science Summer Institute at Google HQ

- · Worked on a three-person team to create a Calendar web application in Python/Django
- $\cdot$  Created a musical android application that recorded and played back sounds & beats created within the app